I don't know
Lewes mixes the ingredients all by himself
I never asked
You silly girl
Something this valuable
He didn't tell you
And you didn't even ask
He's guarding against you
Mom
Don't talk nonsense
Lewes isn't that kind of person
The formula is very complex
And needs adjusting based
on the forest frog's condition
I can't figure it out
That's just an excuse to fool you
How complex can feed be
No way
I'll go see what's actually in this feed
Mom
Don't go
Just relax
When your mom was young
She was a pro at raising pigs
What's in the feed
She can tell at a glance
Locking doors in his own house
Who is he guarding against
Guarding against us
Before workers tried to steal the formula
They kept peeking
And rummaging around in here
So Lewes locked it
No one can go in but him
Don't overthink it
It's against thieves
Not you guys
Let's go
Lewes doesn't like people going near this room